(Penny:)I didn't know you had company.
I don't want to impose.
(Sheldon:)No, no. It's not
an imposition.
(Sheldon:)At this point, in our ecosystem,
you are akin to the plover,
(Sheldon:)a small scavenging bird
that eats extra food
(Sheldon:)from between
the teeth of crocodiles.
(Sheldon:)Please, fly into our open maw,
and have at it.
(Penny:)If I had more than a box of
baking soda in my refrigerator,
(Penny:)I wouldn't have to take that.
(Amy:)Hi, bestie.
(Bernadette:)Hi.
(Penny:)So, um, Priya,
(Penny:)you're a lawyer, right?
(Priya:)I know. Pretty boring, huh?
(Leonard:)Oh, come on.
It's not boring at all.
(Leonard:)She's currently helping set up
a secondary derivative market
(Leonard:)which would allow
overseas car firms
(Leonard:)to hedge their investments
(Leonard:)against potential advancements
in battery technology.
(Leonard:)Hmm?
(Priya:)Thank you, Leonard.
(Priya:)That doesn't make it
sound boring at all.
(Amy:)So, how you holding up?